sonicrun.com 2015-12-04

# Sonic Run: Internet Search Engine

This Privacy Policy covers the Sonic Run treatment of personal information that is recorded when you submit your site for inclusion in our database. Our privacy policy does not apply to the practices of other companies advertised, or otherwise listed, on the Sonic Run website, nor does it extend to people that Sonic Run does not employ or manage. 

**Information Collection and Use**

Sonic Run offers free Standard Listings and paid inclusion Featured Listings. The information we collect is dependent on your needs. 

For Standard Listings, the only information collected is Name, Email Address, and URL. Additional information is collected for Featured Listings, but these can only be purchased at [ExactSeek.com](http://www.exactseek.com/sonicrun.html). 

Your use of Sonic Run services (standard or featured listing of your website or sites) constitutes a business relationship wherein we provide a promotion service for your website(s). In exchange, Sonic Run reserves the right to use the contact information collected during site submission to deliver notices regarding changes or updates to our service, to provide you with a free website monitoring account (FreeWebMonitoring), to inform you of additions to the GreenWave Online Network of websites, or to send announcements and carefully screened offers and information from our partners. 

With the exception of auto-response messages which are sent at the time of site submission and which contain important confirmation details regarding your site listing, you may remove yourself from any or all other notice and announcement mailings at anytime using the unsubscribe methods provided in those mailings. In addition, you may cancel your free website monitoring account at anytime. Any mailing received from our company is clearly identified and includes at least 2 methods to remove yourself from future mailings. Should you encounter problems in this regard, contact: inquiry[at]sonicrun.com. Our turnaround time for responding to unsubscribe requests is generally 24 hours. 

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

Sonic Run maintains your email address and other pertinent personal information, provided at the time of your site submission, on the premises. Sonic Run allows carefully screened vendors the opportunity to send you offers and information that we have deemed may be of value to you. You may opt-in or out of this feature at any time. 

**Cookies**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads and collect data when you visit our website. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements on this site, other sites, and other forms of media about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp 

**Security**

Your personal information is stored in a protected directory. Access is restricted to Sonic Run staff. 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

Sonic Run may amend this policy from time to time. If significant changes are made in the way your personal information is used, we will post a prominent announcement on our site notifying you of the change. 

**Questions or Suggestions**
